<Dialogs>
  <!-- 
Dialog ID = NPC ID 

Dialog ID|NPC Name   |
0        |Piet intro |
1        |Piet       |
2        |Corne      |
3        |Combat tut |
4        |Peter      |
5        |Fer        |
6        |Fedde      |
7        |Sietse     |
-->
  <Dialog Id = "0">
    <Item>Welcome team (player) in the wonderful world of Programon! The world of Programon is full of surprises and magnificent code. But not without danger of course! I have been told that you want to become the best programon team?</Item>
    <Item>Well, you are not then only one. There are many programons to discover, to become the best of the best, you will have to challenge them to a battle. Every programon has its strong and weak points.</Item>
    <Item>Try to adjust your fighting style to your opponents weakness. Good luck and don't forget to pay a visit to me, I could help you to get to your first fight.</Item>
    </Dialog>
    <Dialog Id = "1">
      <Item>Aaah there you are. Thank you for coming over so soon. I have invented a new device, I call it a PCD. It will store all programons you have seen. It also displays information of the programons you are carrying at that moment.</Item>
      <Item>It displays health, experience, level, name and status effects. Last time there was a map around here... Hmmmm where did I left that thing? Well, you should go see Corne, maybe he has a map for you. I probably threw it in the fire, sometimes it could get a little cold and lonely here you know. You can go now, do not forget to speak to Corne for the map, he lives next door. Good luck!</Item>
    </Dialog>
    <Dialog Id = "2">
      <item>"Hey! Who are you!? Get out of my house right now!! Wait… Is that a PCD? Professor Piet gave it to you, didn’t he? Then you must be the one he was talking about. I’m sorry for my rude behavior. I don’t get many visitors you see.</item>
      <Item>Let me introduce myself. My name is Corne. I work at the school in the city. But it was taken over by programons recently. They just came in and began to attack everything!</Item>
      <Item>But I have done some research. It wasn’t just an attack of programons..</Item>
      <Item>It was ordered by a team lead by Sietse and his minions Fer and Fedde. They are currently the best team in the world. If you manage to defeat them you will take their place. But you were here for a map you said?</Item>
      <Item>Here you go! Go fight Sietse and his crew when you are ready. To continue your journey, you should proceed to the next village. In this village is a gym.</Item>
      <Item>Try to defeat the gym master, Peter, if you manage to defeat him he will surely help you to become the best team that ever existed. Maybe he’ll even give the key of the school so you can battle those bastards. Off you go now! And be careful.</Item>
    </Dialog>
  <Dialog Id = "3">
    <Item>Hello stranger, Would you like to know something about combat?</Item>
    <Item>When you get in battle, you will switch to combat mode. Your current equipped programon will automatically be send into battle. There are a few things you will have to know about. First of all is your health bar. When taking damage, the amount of damage that is dealt with will be depleted from your health bar.</Item>
    <Item>If your health is low you can choose to continue the battle with another programon or use an item that replenishes the health of your programon. When your health reaches zero you will have to continue with another programon or flee. Second of all will be the health bar of your opponent of course. When his/her health bar is depeleted you have won the battle.</Item>
    <Item>To attack the programon you will have to choose attack. You will be able to use up to 4 attacks. All attacks deal different amounts of damage. Some attacks will upgrade your abilities or weaken the ones of your opponents. These are called status effects. Use them wisely.</Item>
    <Item>As stated before you can replenish the health of your programon by using an item that will do so. To use an item you will have to select item from the menu. A screen will appear with the items you carry. Choose an item that adds health to your programon to replenish his health.</Item>
    <Item>At lost but not least is the option to flee. If you flee you will leave the battle with no further consequences. Keep in mind though, fleeing is losing. That's it for now. Good luck and code em all.</Item>
  </Dialog>
  <Dialog Id = "4">
    <Item>So, You are the one who’s making all this fuzz. I’ve heard that you want to get to the school to defeat Sietse and take his place as the best team in the world.</Item>
    <Item>Well, It won’t be easy. If you manage to defeat me, I’ll help you to get in the school. Let’s fight!!</Item>
  </Dialog>
  <Dialog Id = "5">
    <Item>Well well well, look who’s here. If it isn’t the one who’s trying to defeat us. You’ll never manage to get passed me!</Item>
  </Dialog>
  <Dialog Id = "6">
    <Item> What!! How have you managed to get passed Fer? Looks like I’ll have to do his work for him. Come on, let’s fight.</Item>
  </Dialog>
  <Dialog Id = "7">
    <Item>Soo you’ve made it. Welcome to my lair. You can’t defeat me, you know that. Why would you even try? But if you are so eager to fight me. You can have it. Bring it on!</Item>
  </Dialog>
</Dialogs>